dcincome.com 2009-03-21

# DCincome.com Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

DCincome.com is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the DCincome.com website and governs data collection and usage. By using the DCincome.com website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. For the purpose of this Privacy Statement, the “DCincome.com Web Site” shall have the same meaning as defined in the DCincome.com Terms Of Use.

DCincome.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are comfortable with any changes. This policy is effective from August 10, 2008.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

DCincome.com collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address and name. DCincome.com may also collect demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

DCincome.com encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from DCincome.com so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. DCincome.com is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of DCincome.com.

**Use of your Personal Information**

DCincome.com collects and uses your personal information to operate the DCincome.com website and deliver the services you have requested. DCincome.com also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from DCincome.com and its affiliates. DCincome.com may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. DCincome.com may also contact you from time to time via your email address to provide you with a variety of information, including weekly wrap ups, newsletters, bulletins and similar information.

DCincome.com does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. DCincome.com may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, DCincome.com may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to DCincome.com, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

DCincome.com does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations.

DCincome.com keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within DCincome.com, in order to determine what DCincome.com services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within DCincome.com to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

DCincome.com websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on DCincome.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of DCincome.com; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of DCincome.com, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**

The DCincome.com website use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize DCincome.com pages, or register with DCincome.com site or services, a cookie helps DCincome.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same DCincome.com website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the DCincome.com features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the DCincome.com services or Web sites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**

DCincome.com secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. DCincome.com secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Changes to this Statement**

DCincome.com will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. DCincome.com encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how DCincome.com is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**

DCincome.com welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that DCincome.com has not adhered to this Statement, please contact DCincome.com support by sending an email to dr.matthew.loop (at) gmail (dot) com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
